<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sayfe</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="exit">press again to exit</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">Sayfe Service</string>
    <string name="sayfe_service_description">This service allows the application to run in the background,
        Hence, to get the best of this application, turn on Sayfe Service</string>
    <string name="contact_permission_denied">Cannot Fetch Contacts because the permission to fetch contacts was denied</string>
    <string name="onboarding_page_demo">onboarding page demo</string>
    <string name="welcome_txt">Welcome to Sayfe \nCreate and send out alerts of insecurity with ease by tapping on volume up button twice</string>
    <string name="getStarted">GET STARTED</string>
    <string name="continueForm">CONTINUE</string>
    <string name="open_settings">GOTO SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="location_permission_txt">To use Sayfe location-based features, please grant permission
        for the app to access your location and send sms once you\'re prompted . This will allow the app to send your real-time location to
        your selected contacts during an emergency, providing them with accurate information to assist you.</string>

    <string name="accessibility_permission_text">To use Sayfe discreet SOS feature triggered via the volume up button,
        please grant the Sayfe accessibility service permission in the settings once prompted. This will allow the app to function seamlessly in the background,
        immediately sending your location information to your selected contacts in case of an emergency.""</string>
    <string name="incoming_alert_txt">Nothing to see here, when you receive a notification, it will appear here</string>
    <string name="outgoing_alert_txt">Nothing to see here, when you send a notification, it will appear here</string>
</resources>